{
    "subject": "resource/Dolores_Guinness",
    "predicate": "ontology/deathDate",
    "object": "2012-01-20",
    "human_readable": "Dolores Guinness passed away on January 20, 2012.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8242919445037842,
            "question": "When did Dolores Guinness pass away?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7758342027664185,
            "question": "Is January 20th a significant date for someone named Dolores Guinness?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7328156232833862,
            "question": "Dolores Guinness's passing was in January. True or False?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6602264642715454,
            "question": "What month and day did Dolores Guinness pass away?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6430355310440063,
            "question": "If today is January 21st, 2013, did Dolores Guinness pass away yesterday?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5913738012313843,
            "question": "What was the date of Dolores Guinness's passing?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5855253338813782,
            "question": "How many years ago did Dolores Guinness pass away?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5814618468284607,
            "question": "In what year did Dolores Guinness die?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.49642619490623474,
            "question": "Was Dolores Guinness alive in 2013?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.25459280610084534,
            "question": "Is it possible to learn more about Dolores Guinness's life?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Dolores Guinness passed away on January 20, 2012.",
            "html": "dbpedia_5536_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Was Dolores Guinness alive in 2013?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5536_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=In what year did Dolores Guinness die?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5536_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How many years ago did Dolores Guinness pass away?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5536_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5536_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5536_109.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5536_118.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5536_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5536_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5536_52.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5536_62.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5536_74.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5536_78.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5536_88.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports the triple. The birthdate of Dolores Guinness is mentioned as July 31, 1936, and her death date is mentioned as January 20, 2012."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe information provided in the documents supports the statement that Dolores Guinness passed away on January 20, 2012. This can be confirmed from the details given in multiple files, which state explicitly that she died on \"20 January 2012\"."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}